how similar does that look to you know I
took my turn signals also I don't want
them I thought I'd picked a cool chick
but this woman is extremely picky that's
a super vibe that's not mine that's a
custom looks like a different frame
she's talking about the different parts
of the motorcycle I don't know what
she's talking about
and I had an idea if you do the front
end coming out of a flower I know I'm
going home if I don't figure out how to
do this definitely feeling color yeah
yeah I think so too right right there we
got the picture I don't understand what
this is
that's the take the other side of the
bike like if you're seeing through it no
you have an extra line there this is
your frame you have to get that pipe
into there okay how the did she go from
liking the drawing to now having a
complete issue this needs to go under
honey is what you're saying here legit
I'm just asking do you want me to
straighten that up there's no way I can
I'm gonna do whatever it takes to get
her to stop complaining and nitpicking
good good I don't finish this tattoo I'm
that be tattooing you can tell that
Ashlee's canvas is pissed and I love it
so motorcycle was the idea yeah like a
drag racing motorcycle see the pixilated
doesn't fit very well with the
motorcycle well that was what I really
wanted to get today may be kind of
difficult one of the things I think is
cool about it is that and that's one
thing you can use to denote the speed
because all the pixels for and off the
back I'm worried that there's a lot of
details we definitely had to go with
some black and gray to make sure that we
get a little detail so you flexible on
that part yeah also nice you're gonna
give me a tattoo it's gonna be a color
tattoo buddy yeah well but with the
what's going on I asked for a color
tattoo
he came and showed me this it's just a
matter of turning this from black and
gray to color he said I can't do this in
color I'm thinking about your skin long
you know I just don't think you can do
what I asked for
now color is not an issue for Mike I
think there was just a miscommunication
there well now I don't trust him why you
didn't listen to me it comes back with
something totally different when I ask
for I don't want to do it with you if I
can't get what I want then I'm done
I am completely screwed right now I
don't do a tattoo today this could be it
I could be going home so look we're
gonna figure out what happens what's
happening guys I need to know the
options at home a customer can leave and
you get another one in here you have to
do a tattoo your thigh open you don't
have to do this tattoo you can do
whatever you want it has to hit the
challenge and you can tattoo yourself
okay or you could tattoo one of the
coaches if they gave you some skin I
hate getting tattooed but I'll go put
some shorts on bro we can do it clean
black and gray rose and pixelated good
pull it up those look at some reference
Michael I really don't want to get
tattooed it looks like pee like the fish
is P is that this bitch is crazy like I
can't figure out how to please or you
tell me that that doesn't look like a
puddle right now the water flows looks
like my nice shirt weer don't insult me
man I have to live with this and you're
not paying for my removals all my face
it mother made it this far and I've been
having all these nutty airs campuses all
this time she's by far the worst this is
the us right now like
he's too orange don't look like a
pumpkin and vent it but I've told your
skin irritated I'm trying to be nice and
I'm with your people I'm trying too late
talk to you so we can work together well
I do know this if you guys want to try
to finish this tattoo you need this you
told me to stop I was trying to say at
least let me finish what I started your
job is to work with me here it's gonna
make me flip out you know what I mean
it's time to find out who the human
canvas jury determined had the worst
tattoo of the day
[Music]
Kito I think anybody else to what they
had to deal with what I dealt with would
have probably been down here to excuse
me
you messed up my back and you can't take
full responsibility for that I'll be
tattooed
I ended up giving in and pretty much
letting her coach the whole drawing
that's not my work that was all you and
it looks horrible I don't like the
lining for colors the flower placement I
don't like the water placement at all
you're dealing with an awful work that
you just did on my back unfortunately I
have to live with for like ever
okay getting that I'm just too
intelligent man finally with butter
right now just leave that there
[Music]
robots are not biomechanical what I
showed you original robots mechanical or
not but yes if you don't meet the
challenge even if you Joe can you let me
finish my canvas is a straight up ass we
need to have some respect right now I'm
trying to be respectful but you're not
compromising you could do that style
Somaly the challenge is this style so
how can I do it some if the challenge is
this style give me some direction or got
punching some don't feel like punching
film oh oh my children are depending on
me right now and his things he wants in
this tattoo are going to send me home
and I can't let that happen you need to
go so I can get to work right but I want
to see what you go how you doing all
right so this is what I've come up with
I got the cables coming around and then
we have the vile part which is what
they're looking for if you don't like it
I'm just gonna tattoo it on myself yeah
not really feeling it right going
you should I mean there's just nothing
I'm trying to work with her and she's
not willing to work with me not one bit
are you willing to compromise a little
bit no because you really didn't put
anything cables of metal tattooing
myself I compromised a lot of compromise
will do a great tattoo no you don't you
kept saying all kinds of I'm not putting
questions no I didn't say I said bye
have a nice life yourself Julia there
were some unusual circumstances with you
and your canvas before we get into that
let's discuss the work that you have
presented for us this is probably the
strongest thing as a judge I've seen you
do it has a lot of contrast that has a
lot of depth so now let's talk about
what happened in your consult
I was trying really hard to be very
patient but the guy just kept cutting me
off and I was just like I'm trying to
work with you I'm trying to do what you
want and then at one point he shushed me
so I was just like look this is the
design and if you don't want to do it
I'm just gonna tattoo it on myself at
this point there are two sides to every
story maybe we should hear from your
canvas
[Music]
for me what is your side of the story
she hated every idea that I had she said
they were all crap she said they're all
so outdated she just said I have to do
her tattoo but I wasn't getting a tattoo
and I said well can't you just change
anything she's like I will not change
nothing I was on the computer the whole
time just like well let me show you this
let me show you this so I was like just
tell me the components you want then
yeah you were super rude about it I've
never ever seen any artist treat a
customer so rudely and terribly we heard
your side Julia we heard his side all of
us watched 100% the entire footage of
every minute that y'all two were
together his side is almost spot-on the
truth your side is spin-doctor to hell
you told him to go himself unprovoked
Lee told him to go himself my canvas
wants a Sun and a moon tattoo on her
upper back you know we might not even
need this all around I mean no we do
what I'm trying to figure out now is the
design it's almost impossible because
she's constantly contradicting herself
I don't want the face so I can use like
I mean you couldn't do the face what's
you I mean you don't say it's up to me
because then you just change your mind
instantly I know what you actually do
you have another idea what do you want
it's basically a heart it's your call
right now well like definitely need to
settle on something
you said you didn't really want a
cartoony so when I colored it darker oh
whoa that's on the ball I'm very proud
of you my canvas has like five
personalities she goes from being psycho
crazy to give me hogs just crazy check
it out that's a little high you want to
go Lord yeah she's got a couple weird
request but she's being a good client
deciding the truth it looks ugly okay
you see those three spikes but doesn't
look right you kept telling me to do
whatever I want you went overboard with
those things I don't like it at all
that's not in the drawing why did you do
that you're freaking me oh my god all
right we have to fix this
for some reason the five little magenta
spikes I had totally destroyed the
entire tattoo for her this is insane who
added that without telling me why would
you say that more magenta I said yes you
didn't say magenta spikes that is not my
style if someone's not happy with her
Minette work that's on their body it's a
really justified reason to freak out
[Music]